<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MADE-Submission-1</string>
    <string name="lorem">lorem</string>

    <string-array name="data_title_movie">
        <item>Avengers : Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
        <item>A Star Is Born </item>
        <item>Mortal Engines</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>Joker</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_image_movie">
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mortalengine</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_joker</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_rating">
        <item>83 %</item>
        <item>80 %</item>
        <item>65 %</item>
        <item>66 %</item>
        <item>75 %</item>
        <item>61 %</item>
        <item>68 %</item>
        <item>75 %</item>
        <item>84 %</item>
        <item>68 %</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="status">
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_description">
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too
            large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows
            Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity
            Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all
            of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment the fate
            of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist
            John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock n roll band Queen in
            1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercurys increasingly wild lifestyle
            starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet finding a
            way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.
        </item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small
            Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place
            in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him,
            she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.
        </item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but
            accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon,
            he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization
            looking for a symbiote of their own.
        </item>
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers and falls in love with struggling artist
            Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer until Jack
            coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Allys career takes off, the personal side of
            their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own
            internal demons.
        </item>
        <item>Many thousands of years in the future, Earth’s cities roam the globe on huge wheels,
            devouring each other in a struggle for ever diminishing resources. On one of these
            massive traction cities, the old London, Tom Natsworthy has an unexpected encounter with
            a mysterious young woman from the wastelands who will change the course of his life
            forever.
        </item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater
            kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans
            to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way
            is Arthur Curry, Orms half human, half Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.
        </item>
        <item>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys
            to save a boys life.
        </item>
        <item>During the 1980s, a failed stand up comedian is driven insane and turns to a life of
            crime and chaos in Gotham City while becoming an infamous psychopathic crime figure.
        </item>
        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent
            with ties to his familys past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.
        </item>
    </array>
</resources>
